bartcop.com 2013-05-21

# BartCop.com - Privacy Policy at BartCop.com and BartBlog

    At BartCop.com, we respect your privacy and are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our sites www.bartcop.com and bartblog.bartcop.com. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

    **Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers, we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

    **Cookies and Web Beacons  
**A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. Our site use cookies for tracking visitors’ activity and other uses that might include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some specific features. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. You can choose not to accept cookies by modifying your browser settings. At any time, you may remove any cookie stored on your hard drive by deleting them in your browser’s settings section.

**Advertisers**  
We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and we do not have access to these information. We work with the ad companies: Google Adsense, Feedburner and blogads. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Contact Information**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at bartcop (at) bartcop.com
